

Luis José Meza

Project Manager & Junior Full-Stack Developer

Phone Numbers:

- +503 2563-4852
- +503 7264-5905

Email:

luisjosemeza90@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/luis-josémeza-garcia-80763267

Location:

Antiguo Cuscatlán, La Libertad El Salvador

Personal Profile

I consider myself a quick learner and put full effort to all tasks assigned to me.

I am eager to use my English in an International company while at the same time use French and Spanish when necessary in international situations.

I am a highly motivated person who is looking for continuous improvement and new ways to collaborate in a company.

Educational Training

Udemy (Online Course Platform)

September 2019 - May 2020

Full Web Development Course: HTML5, CSS3, JS AJAX,PHP & MYSQL

Ecole Superieure de Commerce de Rennes

Rennes, France

Master in Logistics & Innovation Management

- From Sept. 2012 to June 2016
- Major in Supply chain management and Innovation

Universite Rennes 2 Haute Bretagne

Rennes, France

Bachelor of Arts: Communication Technologies

- From Sept. 2009 to Sept.2012
- Acquiring the knowledge on Law, Economics and major issues in Communication.

Professional Skills

Coding Languages:

JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Java, PHP

Frameworks/Systems:

ReactJS, bootstrap, Visual Studio Code, MySQL, Sourcetree, Bitbucket, Eclipse IDE

Languages:

- Spanish • • 100%
- French • • 100%
- English • 90

Career Summary

Quality Management Project Specialist

PBS El Salvador Antiguo Cuscatlán Oct 2018 to June 2020

- Identified plans and resources required to meet project goals and objectives by setting realistic timelines and checkpoints.
- Developed implementation methodologies to rein in project costs while meeting key milestones.
- Orchestrated projects within strict time frames and budget constraints by solving complex problems and working closer with senior leaders.

Customer Service Representative

The Office Gurus Santa Tecla March 2018 – July 2018

 Provide full customer service on the account Rise (online Lender Company US based). In charge of assisting customers over their accounts, profiles, payments and requests via phone and e-mail.

Character References

Guillermo Rodriguez Perdomo

General Manager, PBS Guatemala E-mail: guillermo.rodriguez@grouppbs.com Cell: +503 7862 6003

Ernesto Andres Rivas Fuentes

Store Sub-Manager, Almacenes Siman Email: ernesto_rivas@siman.com Cell: +503 7523 7304